《夏日亡魂》 前情提要
Previously on "Dead of Summer"...
我要走了
I got to go.
我做e什N了 克瑞克特
What did I do? Cricket!
你到底是l
Who are you?
你f^你接受真正的我的
Look, you said you could accept me.
-布R -每次我看到你
- Blair... - Every time I see you,
你好像都在拍z什N|西
you seem to be filming something.
俗f得好
You know what they say.
z像^牟撒e
The camera never lies.
我X得我能和你聊一晚上
I feel like I could talk to you all night.
f心 她都和你差不多大了
Gross. She's like your mother's age.
戴伯可能ψ约旱纳矸萦兴[m
Deb might not be who she says she is.
戴伯不是娜
Deb is not Satanic.
可如果她是的 克瑞克特不就fα
If she was, isn't Cricket right?
她肯定不f出戆
Wouldn't she hide it?
可我_知道@翰
But I do know something is going on here.
你有]有想^
You ever think it's possible...
@些|西有可能是真的
that some of it could be real?
那高男人f^「@才只是_始」
The Tall Man has said, "It's only just begun."
你希望我fc什N
Do you expect me to talk?
不用 邦德先生
No, Mr. Bond.
我只希望你英勇奚
I expect you to die.
看看@
Oh, check it out, Joel!
你X得我能在舞上扮成007
Do you think I could pass as 007 at prom?
也S吧
Maybe...
如果大家都瞎了眼的
If everyone there was blind.
好咯
Oh, okay.
我想念你的 弟弟
You know, I'm gonna miss you, bro.
再^字 你就得去夏令IY了 夥
A few more weeks, you'll be off at camp, man.
我希望你能和我一起去
I wish you could come with me.
不了 我已在清水市有^自己的回了
Nah, I've had my own experience with Stillwater.
你需要去H自w一下
You got to experience it for yourself.
在那一人的孩子 ]人相信我和你是H兄弟的
As the geeky kid that nobody can believe is related to you?
你穿著@ 看他不叫你鬼
Let's see them call you geeky in that.
@都能b下四我了
I could fit four of me in this.
@就要看你怎N穿了
It depends how you wear it.
人的感X能打‖F
Perception beats reality every time.
我不敢相信你要送我你最喜g的衣服
I can't believe you're giving me your favorite shirt.
等你A了W斯卡再砀兄x我吧 好
Just thank me when you win your first Oscar, okay?
成交
Deal.
@才是我弟弟
My man.
~克 怎N了
What's wrong, Michael?
你是不是 看到什N了
Did you... see something?
我 我看到一小砘 他害得我⒓游快要t到啦
Uh, I-I see a kid who's gonna make me late for prom, man.
走吧 我得so收拾好自己 小砘
Come on, I got to get out of here, punk.
我得去_澡 然後在豪AI到@之前
I got to get showered and get this tux on
穿好Y服
before the limo gets here.
e@勇 大家
Come on, guys.
有半小r我就得出l了
We're supposed to hit the trail in a half hour.
-你@是质颤N -除非我得到想要的答案
- What are you doing? - We're not going anywhere
不然我是不x_的
till we get some answers.
什N答案
About what?
昨晚
Last night.
是啊 你和戴伯昨晚消失去哪毫
Yeah, where'd you and Deb disappear to?
你是J真的
Seriously?
她 有е那人的面具
She, uh, bring that creepy mask with her?
我一直很心你
We were worried about you.
只是我中的某些人
Some of us.
那面具根本不是她的
That mask isn't even hers.
行了 你都`戴伯了
Okay, you guys have the wrong idea about Deb.
夥 你和她打了一炮啊
Yo, man. You totally banged her!
你f什N
What?
不 我才]有
No, I didn't.
有 你有
Yeah, you did.
而且我知道你都在z影CY了
And I know you got it on that camera.
砺 我看看
Come on, let me check it out.
砺 我就看一眼
-你都啦 -得了吧
- You guys are crazy! - Come on, Joel!
你才是那和大了你杀q档娜L床蔚砘
You're the one who had sex with someone twice your age.
我想 快f
We want details... now.
@嘛 你和德在化y舞上恿苏娓星檎O
Well, you and Drew got pretty serious at the masquerade.
你槭颤N不o我vv
Why don't you give us some of those details?
P於@一c
And on that note...
-好吧 -
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-W人 -W人
好啦 大家快c
All right, come on!
我要在高草地上野I啦
We're gonna make camp at High Meadow!
我要好づ 要煮晚
We're gonna pitch our tents and then cook dinner.
你在那Y能看到天上的每一w星星
You guys will get to see every star in the sky from up there,
今晚有血月出F
and there's a Blood Moon tonight,
所以特e延^的
so it'll be extra awesome.
大家都跟o克瑞克特
Everyone follow Cricket's lead.
她是我的敉庖I＜
She is our resident outdoor specialist.
x小夥伴 待在FY
Pick a partner, stay in groups,
千f不要走散了
and don't wander off the path!
@森林Y到都藏著捕熊陷阱
There are bear traps hidden everywhere in these woods.
你真的很喜g她
You really like her, huh?
P於昨晚的疑惑 我很抱歉
I'm sorry about the confusion last night.
如果我早知道
If we had known...
]事的 不用心
Yeah, don't worry about it.
我知道@跟我]什NPS
I know it's none of my business,
不^我X得你 挺棒的
but I think it's great... you two.
l在意e人怎Nf
Who cares what they say?
能和一人a生共Q俨灰
It's not easy to make a connection with someone.
如果你@N幸\地找到了
If you're lucky enough to find it,
你就努力取 Π
you should go for it, right?
Right.
嗷
Boo!
嘿 嘿 l生什N了
Hey, hey, what's going on?
阿R克斯f淞盅Y有一b怪物
Alex said there's a monster in these woods!
是的 一b吃人肉的食乒
Yeah, a flesh-eating ghoul
它最喜g喝野I的人的血了
with a taste for camper blood.
我走吧
Let's go.
就玩玩嘛 芪
Whatever, Jessie.
-e@勇 -拜 阿R克斯
-Come on. -Bye, Alex.
嘿 你好
Hey, are you okay?
我不能呼吸了
I can't breathe.
我想她需要她的吸入器 就在她背包最上面的袋子Y
I think she needs her inhaler. It's in the top of her bag.
好的 我拿到了
All right, I got it.
]事的 放p
It's gonna be okay, just relax.
就是@
There you go.
感X好些了
Better?
e心 弗朗茜 @只是故事
Don't worry, Francie. It's just a story.
森林Y]有怪物要害你
Nothing in these woods will hurt you.
我跟你保C
I promise.
好吧
Okay.
那行 和芪饕黄鹱甙
All right, go with Jessie.
]事的
It's okay.
艾米
Amy.
快o我走_
Leave me alone.
你好
Are you okay?
你是不是看到什N了
Did you see something?
]有
Nope.
我挺好的
I'm good.
可以了 f茄子
Okay, say cheese.
笑一
Smile.
你哥哥怎N@N久]好
What is taking your brother so long?
子已在等了
Limo's waiting.
我去叫他
I'll go get him.
~克
Michael?
Michael?!
好 阿R克斯和克瑞克特 你柴火
Okay, Alex and Cricket, firewood detail.
德和布R 你去安排食物
Drew and Blair, get the food organized.
艾米和芪 我需要男∠Y取c水
Amy and Jessie, we need water from the stream.
有  你就和我待在@
And, Joel, you'll stay back with me
臀野づ穸即詈
and help me pitch the tents.
嘿 祝你搭戴伯的小づ翊畹糜淇
Hey, have fun pitching Deb's tent.
你知道我的
You know I will.
喔
Oh.
艾米
Amy.
怎N了
Yeah?
小心c
Um, be careful out there.
真有必要看@
Is that really necessary?
我在T工休息室Y找到的
I found it in the staff lounge.
我想能派上用
I figured it could come in handy,
竟是我第一次在森林Y^夜
being my first overnight and all.
嘿 好
Hey, is everything okay with Joel?
他看起碛悬c恍惚
He seemed kind of off.
也S是因樗不像加勒特一幽屈N狂地迷倌
Maybe he's just not as taken with you as Garrett.
你f什N
Excuse me?
昨晚我看到你的舌^都要伸M他喉笛Y了
I saw you last night with your tongue down his throat.
-我不懂你在f什N -艾米 eb了好
- I am so confused. - Amy, just stop, okay?
我看到你接吻了
I saw you guys kissing.
可我根本不得跟他H^啊
I don't remember kissing him at all.
最近@Yl生了特e多的事情
So many freaky things have been going on here.
是@地方的原因
It's this place.
不 是你自己的} e再遮遮掩掩b白了
No, it's you. Stop putting up a front.
如果你喜g他的 直f就好了
If you're into him, just say so.
如果你喜g他的 你就f啊
If you're into him, you say so.
你在瞎f什N啊
What are you talking about?
@Y遮遮掩掩的人就只有你一
The only one putting up a front here is you.
而且加勒特不是你所有老朋友中唯一一
And Garrett's not the only one of your old friends
不喜g你@友b白的
who doesn't like it.
Joel.
你能把那z像C放下一N
Can you put the camera down for a second?
我需要
I could, um...
我需要你臀乙幌
I could use a hand.
我 我不能把@子牢在地Y
I, uh... I can't get the stake to stay in the ground.
好的 好的 我@就
Yeah, yeah. One second.
我戆
Allow me.
弄好了
There you go.
再也]有|西能把@子o弄出砹
Nothing is knocking this thing down.
除非是《激流四勇士》的演TQ定F身搞破
Unless the cast of "Deliverance" Decides to show up.
每次我去野I我都想起@部影
I think about that movie every time I go camping.
l不是呢
How can you not?
想Mづ裱Y一下
Want to test it out from the inside,
看看@づ袷遣皇翘乩喂
make sure it's extra sturdy?
唔
Um...
你f什N
What?
我想f 要超越昨晚是有cy
I mean, it'd be hard to top last night,
不^我_信我能再努力看
but I'm sure we could try.
你是f化y舞
You mean the masquerade?
你真有趣
You're funny.
好啦 我知道了
Yeah, I get it.
@rg和地c_都不太合m
It's not the time or the place.
也S再晚c吧
Maybe later.
你好
You all right, Joel?
我很好啊
Yeah.
只是你和某人a生如此烈的共Qr
It's just that when you really make a connection with somebody,
那感X真的很美妙
it's pretty great.
xx你 你真N心
That's sweet. Thank you.
^Σ灰把@身衣服弄了
No way I'm doing ruffles.
嘿 e拍我 肯尼 我看起砭拖
Hey, don't film this, Kenny. I look like a...
大K^
A hunk?
你是想f呆瓜
You mean dork?
嘿
Hey.
e理他 你一c都不像傻瓜
Come on, there's nothing dorky about you, babe.
你看起硐007
You look like Bond.
是 哪 是康{利是摩演的
Yeah? Which one... Connery or Moore?
拉森比演的
Mm, Lazenby.
啊你真是
Ow! You just...
好了啦 你比其他男的多了
Come on, you're a million times hotter than all those guys,
你知道的 我X途o量的
and you know it, Mr. Golden Boy,
你都被~s大W影W院提前取了
early acceptance to NYU Film School.
你最好我⒀菽愕乃有影
You better put me in all your movies.
-你不知道 -什N
- Oh, you didn't know? - Hmm?
你已是我其中一部影的主演了
You're already in one of my movies.
名字叫《衣g》
It's called "The Fitting Room."
-e -砺 看R^
- Stop! - Come on, come on.
你要是想演我的影 就不能那N害羞
You can't be shy if you're gonna be in my movies.
不不 放下z像C
No, no, put it down. Joel!
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.
Joel?
你怎N了
What are you doing?
]什N
Nothing.
你不打算臀乙幌
Are you gonna help me at all?
我也想 但是
I would love to, but, uh...
@根怎N
How's this one?
不怎N
No, not that one.
太脆了
Too flimsy?
太嫩了 c燃冒 但是不燃
Too green. It'll smoke, not burn.
你真的是夜雠王啊
You really are still queen of the overnight, aren't you?
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
嘿 得我以前叫你戴S・克瑞克特
Hey, remember when we used to call you Davy Cricket?
嗯 我得你是那N叫我的
Yeah, I remember you calling me that
而我很@名字
and me hating it.
得了吧 你挺喜g的
Oh, come on, you liked it.
你就承J吧
Come on, admit it.
你小心c
What are you doing?
我告V^你了 @|西到都是
I told you, they're everywhere.
哇
Whoa.
@不好笑 你心c
Not funny. You should keep your eyes open.
我都得小心c
We all should.
槭颤N
And why is that?
因檫@些捕熊陷阱不只是唯一
Because bear traps aren't the only thing
我要心的|西
we should be worried about.
即使不是戴伯
Even if it wasn't Deb,
我是看到有人戴著那面具
I still saw someone in that mask.
@不是我想像出淼
I didn't imagine it,
而且他有可能在@Y
and they could still be out there.
你知道 看起
You know, it seems like...
你需要ce的事情磙D移你的注意力
you need something else to focus on.
是
Oh, yeah?
是的
Yeah.
我在想 今晚熄翎
You know, I was thinking, maybe I'd come here tonight,
也S我磉@Y 砜囱月
after lights out, and watch the Blood Moon.
你想一起
You want to join?
你的意思是我想不想和你在血月下做
You mean, do I want to have sex with you under the Blood Moon?
我可]那Nf
I did not say that.
我知道你是什N拥娜
I know you.
也S我了呢 克瑞克特
Maybe I've changed, Cricket.
又或者也S我是第一拒^你的女孩呢
Or maybe I'm the first girl that's ever turned you down,
而你o法接受@事
and you can't handle it.
好好欣p血月吧
Enjoy the Blood Moon.
「xφ_的木棍是
"The right stick is essential
烤出|棉花糖的PI」
to the perfectly roasted marshmallow."
我有一根
I've got one.
真棒
Nice!
我交Q一下吧
Here, let's switch.
看著c 兄弟
Watch out, buddy.
抱歉
Oh, sorry about that.
]PS
That's okay.
I舞照的
Prom date?
嘿
Hey.
你看上去好_心
You guys look happy.
是啊
We were.
在看
Studying up?
多知道c不有e Π
Couldn't hurt, right?
再f了 你之前好像很心我
Plus, you did seem worried about me earlier.
是的 抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
我可能有c想多了
Guess I was a little paranoid.
那你F在]事了吧
You're good now, though?
是的
Yeah.
好了 我看看 你烤得怎N
Okay, let's see. How you doing?
今晚 ⒘ 艾米
Kill... Amy... tonight.
不然其他人就死
Or someone else will die.
布R
Blair.
克瑞克特最喜g的歌是什N
What's Cricket's favorite song?
槭颤N@N
Why?
@N多致
What do you care why?
是不是直男被女孩拒^了
Is this that thing that straight guys do
就@N做啊
when girls reject them?
快 最喜g的歌 很蔚}
Come on, favorite song... easy answer.
布洛特已o她做了一P混音Я
Blotter already made her a mix tape.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
我希望也S他忘了某一首歌
I was hoping maybe he'd forgotten a track.
他_忘了
He did, actually.
《迷人的月亮》 回c兔人逢的
"The Killing Moon," Echo & the Bunnymen,
她一直都很喜g
her all-time favorite.
-《迷人的月亮》 -嗯哼
- "Killing Moon"? - Mm-hmm.
好的
Okay.
你有《迷人的月亮》@首歌 德斯基
Hey, you got "Killing Moon," Drewski?
去我づ裱Y拿
Grab it from my tent.
有 不要再叫我德斯基了
Also, never call me Drewski again,
不然我就⒘四
or I will end your life.
好吧
Fair enough.
你真是酷
That was really cool of you.
著 我很理解你槭颤N生我
Look, I don't blame you for being mad at me.
我只是想f
I just wanted to say...
我o^你C了
Okay, you had your chance.
再o多我次C吧
Well, I'm asking for another one.
你告V我你是l
You showed me who you are.
我告V你我是l 有什N好f的
I showed you who I was. What's left to say?
天啊
Oh, God!
有人忘了在Y面放冰K了
Someone forgot to put ice in there.
Ugh.
好了 ]PS
Okay. It's okay.
我有一些峁 在I地那
Um, there's hot dogs, uh, down at the camp.
我不去
Not it!
我去拿吧
I'll go.
xx你
Thank you.
⒘怂
Kill her.
艾米 e去
Amy, don't go.
槭颤N
Why not?
呃
Uh...
她不JR路
She doesn't know these woods.
那你和她一起去
So go with her.
跟著她
Follow her.
等她一人的r候 ⒘怂
When she's alone, kill her.
不
No.
No?
好了
Okay.
艾米 你是和孩子待在一起吧
Uh, Amy, you're better with the kids.
我和芪魅
Jessie and I will go.
很好
Exactly.
@是你的x
It's your choice.
她不死
Her...
其他人就死
or someone else will die.
哇
Ow!
你看到了 诶 今天走凸棚L
Do you see this, Laura? I went old-school.
我租了白色的豪AI I了m花
I got the white limo. I got the... orchid.
我甚至I通了DJ
I'm even gonna bribe the deejay
他放你最鄣拉・阿巴杜的歌曲
to play that Paula Abdul song you love.
今晚肯定很完美
It's gonna be a perfect night.
你想质颤N
What do you want?!
你在哪Y
Where are you?
我要把@o警察看
I'm showing this to the cops!
嘿
Hey!
-爸爸 -你好
- Oh, Dad. - You okay?
我 我到你在大叫
I, uh... I heard you yelling.
是的 我只是
Yeah, uh, I was just...
@|西 我系不好
this thing is... I can't figure it out.
我有c罕
I got frustrated.
所以我想著出硗饷婧粑一下新r空
I figured I'd just come outside and get some fresh air.
我湍憷M好
Here, let me help you out.
你得慢慢_始T穿Y服了
Now, you better get used to wearing a tux.
今晚⒓赢I舞 明天就去艾美CY
Tonight the prom, tomorrow the Emmys.
是W斯卡  W斯卡才是影 爸爸
Oscars. It's Oscars for movies, Dad.
好吧 o是什N
Yeah, well, whatever it is,
我都坐在前排最中g 槟慵佑
I will be there front row and center, cheering you on.
xx你爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
你o
Are you nervous?
o今晚
About tonight?
我只是在想~克
I'm just thinking about Michael.
在I舞那晚
Prom night.
他有告V^你他看到什N了
Did he ever tell you what he saw?
]有 ]f^
No, he never would.
我不知道他看到什N了
We didn't know what he was seeing
或者f槭颤N他那N害怕
or why he was so... so scared of it.
我和他
Me and him.
我是f 那]什N的Π
I mean, it doesn't matter, does it?
o他看到什N了 那都不是真的
Whatever he saw, it wasn't real.
只是他自己想多了
Just a sickness in his mind.
感x上帝
I thank God
你永h 都不用去面δ噩
that you will never... never have to face that nightmare.
你_定你好
Are you sure you're okay?
你知道 ol生什N了
You know, whatever it is,
你都可以告V我 好
you know you can tell me, right?
可能我是有c壕o
Maybe I'm a little nervous.
不想诶失望
Don't want to disappoint Laura.
你不的
You won't.
嘿
Hey.
怎N了 孩子好吧
What's up? Kids okay?
嗯 孩子都好
Yeah, kids are okay.
唔
Um...
但是我不好
But I'm not.
我有A感有些事情要l生
I had a feeling something was up.
怎N回事
What is it?
我以前]告V^任何人
I've never told anyone this before.
]PS
It's all right. Yeah.
我X得我和你心有`犀
I feel like I have a connection with you.
是的
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
你在质颤N
What are you doing?
我以
I thought...
你以槭颤N
You thought what?
我想椭你  我真的想
I want to help, Joel, I do,
但是我 我仍然是你的上司
um, but I'm... I'm still your boss.
你在f什N呢 你仍然是我的上司
What are you talking about, you're still my boss?
那昨晚的事算什N
What about last night?
你不能b作什N都]有l生^一
You can't just act like that didn't happen.
b作]l生^什N呢
Act like what didn't happen?
我去散步了 我告V了你基思的事情
We went for a walk. I told you about Keith.
H此而已
That's... it.
呃
Um...
不如你告V我到底l生什N了
Why don't you tell me what's really going on.
我想 只是
Um, I... I... I guess I just...
我想太多了
I read more into it.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
]事的
It's okay.
我要走了
Uh, I'm gonna go.
你]法我消失
You can't make me go away.
我不消失 除非你⒌舭米
Not here, not until you kill Amy.
住 你才是f了算的 好
Remember, you're the boss, okay?
e小小的棉花糖A^你
Don't let the marshmallow win.
你去
You should go.
去赴他的血月之s
To his Blood Moon rendezvous?
不了xx
No, thanks.
我X得他已了
I think he's changed.
拜
Please.
他就是辣u 你是知道的
He's a dirt bag, and you know it.
如果他只想和你上床的
If all he wanted was to sleep with you,
槭颤N他我你最喜g的歌是什N呢
why would he ask me what your favorite song is?
他你我最喜g的歌了
He asked you my favorite song?
是啊
Yeah.
他是真的很用心
He's putting himself out there.
o他C吧
Just give him the chance.
你快]rg了
You're running out of time.
e@N做
Don't do that.
你受的
You could hurt yourself.
Joel.
⒌舭米
Kill Amy.
她不死 e人就得死
Her, or someone else will die.
是l死呢
Who will it be?
你快]rg了
You're running out of time.
是l死呢
Who's it gonna be?
Joel?
你的相C呢
Where's your camera?
你平r都一直拿著它的呀
It's usually attached to your hand.
相C]用了
It's not working.
牧
Is it broken?
相C在@Y]用
It doesn't work here.
-啊 -啊
- Ah. - Ah.
那照得好
That was a good one.
我眼睛]上了 我想重新再照一
My eyes were closed. I want a do-over.
你看起砻O了
You looked gorgeous, babe.
砺
Come on.
等下 你е相C啊
Wait, you're bringing that?
是啊 今晚可是我的I舞
Yeah, it's... it's our prom night.
你不想永h住今晚
Don't you want to remember this forever?
今晚是P於我的 P於我的回
Tonight's about us, our memories.
@K不需要相C
You don't need a camera for that.
嘿 诶 ^
Hey, Laura, come here.
好的
Okay.
你不是真的
You're not real.
你在和lf
Who are you talking to?
]人
No one.
呃
Uh...
好了 你f得 我R上回
All right, you're right. I'll be right back.
我去把相C存起
I'm just gonna go check this.
嘿 玩得怎N
Hey, how's it going?
o你
Here you go.
是的 我能湍捍嫦C
Yeah, I can take that for you.
x了
Thanks.
我在等什N啊
What are we waiting for, huh?
你浜锰舞了
Oh, you ready to dance, or what?
^
Get over here.
_始吧
Huh?
o布R一C吧
I mean, cut Blair some slack.
他 他 他了我
He... he's... He ran out on me.
那又怎N F在他想要跟你和好了
So? Now he wants to un-run.
你完全不知道σ人那N坦白是什N感X
You have no idea what it's like to be that open with someone.
你甚至都不敢告V克斯
You can't even tell Sykes
你要上法庭的事
about your court date.
我就是ff而已
Just saying.
那是什N
What's that?
我X得那就是阿R克斯和艾米s的小屋
I think that's the cabin that Alex took Amy on their date.
有情{
Hot.
你在@质颤N呢
What are you doing here?
我在巡
I'm patrolling camp
大家都去淞盅Y^夜了啊
while everyone else is supposed to be on the overnight,
你怎N]和他一起
so why aren't you with them?
我本硎且黄鸬
We were.
我
We
我是和他一起
We are. Hmm.
好了 我肀尺@
Okay. Um, I'm gonna take this.
你知道怎N回去的Π
You know how to get back, right?
-是的 -很好
- Yeah. - Great.
你怎N想到要磉@Y
So, what brings you out here?
我要M去
Going in there.
你想有人陪
Do you want some company?
好啊
Sure.
@是什N地方
What is this place?
就是f的C房
It's just an old hunting cabin.
你真不撒e
You're a terrible liar.
@是我M行的{查中的一部分
It's part of an investigation I'm conducting.
什N{查
Into what?
你知道清水曾是招魂者I地
Did you know Stillwater was a Spiritualist camp?
噢 就像艾米f的那些邪教徒
Oh, like those cultists Amy was talking about?
她告V你了
She told you?
@不是什N秘密吧
I didn't realize it was a secret.
你致镞@N小心翼翼的
Why are you being so cagey?
1871年的r候@小屋被突u了
There was a raid on this cabin in 1871.
@些人追S著一叫做霍利尤克的招魂者首I
They were after a Spiritualist leader named Holyoke.
湖Y的人都是他的信徒
People in the lake were his followers.
他怎N了
What happened to them?
@邪教常遭遇到的事
The same thing that always happens with these cults.
所有人都死了
Everybody dies.
但是@都是一百多年前的事了 槭颤N你要
But this was over 100 years ago. Why are you...
因槲矣X得可能
Because I still think
有些信徒在@附近活
there might be some followers kicking around.
你在逗我吧
Come on, seriously?
昨晚 我看湖有群人
Last night, I saw these people down by the lake.
他戴著面具
They were wearing these masks.
昨晚可是化y舞
Well, it was a masked ball.
我的意思是 l都有可能戴著面具
I mean, they could have been anyone.
可能吧
Yeah, maybe.
但我是想z查一下@地方
But I still wanted to come check this place out,
_保]人在@鹤淌
make sure nobody's been digging around,
有什N歪主意
getting ideas.
看
Look.
@特N是啥
What the hell is that?
在十九世o人就用@碛事情
This is how people used to record things in the 19th century.
霍利尤克 就是你f的那人
"Holyoke"... that's the guy you were just talking about.
就是他 Π
That's him, right?
有e的|西
There's something else.
那是什N 硬
What is that, a coin?
是袖扣
It's a cufflink.
JS
J.S.
芸恕べ克斯
Jack Sykes.
@是我爸爸的
This belonged to my father.
你X得她
You think she's gonna come?
只有一k法_J
Only one way to find out.
去那旱人
Get down there and wait for her.
@我能做到 x了
I can do that. Thanks.
嘿
Hey!
你去哪
Where you going?
去欣p血月
Uh, to watch the Blood Moon.
一人
Alone?
希望不是
Hopefully not.
有什N}
Is there a problem?
小心c
Just be careful.
肯定的啦 老爸
Sure thing, Dad.
嘿 xx你的磁 兄弟
Hey, um... thanks for the tape, buddy.
嗯 我也不喜g「兄弟」@Q呼
Yeah, I don't like "Buddy," Either.
嘿
Hey.
祝你好\ 我希望她去赴s
Good luck. I hope she shows.
x了
Thanks.
芪髂
Where's Jessie?
她和克斯在一起
She's with Sykes.
她好
Is she okay?
她挺好的 你@是怎N了
She's fine. What's wrong with you?
我只是想_J一下她好
I'm just making sure that she's okay.
嘿
Hey.
我想_J所有人的安全
That everyone's safe.
]人安全
No one is.
]人安全 除非你⒌舭米
No one is until you kill Amy.
夥
Guys.
戴伯我F在都^去
Deb needs us now.
你把它G在哪了 甜心
Where did you leave it, sweetheart?
-你得 -l生什N了
- Do you remember? - What happened?
她把她的吸入器弄G了
She lost her inhaler.
如果我]法找到的 她就不能呼吸了
She can't breathe if we don't get it back.
不然e人就死
Or someone else will die.
嘿 弗朗茜 你X得
Hey, Francie, do you think
你有可能把它落在我早些r候停下的地方
you might have left it where we stopped earlier?
-是 -我去找找
- Yeah? - I'll go get it.
-我和你一起去 -不
- I'll go with you. - No.
你就呆在@Y
You stay here.
嘿 著 也S艾米和你一起去
Hey, listen, maybe Amy should go.
你最近有c不在B
You've been a little out of sorts lately.
不 我可以的
No, I can do this.
我必去
I have to do this.
拿著@
Here, take this.
以防f一
Just in case.
你有e的事要去做
You have something else to do.
不 她不死的
No. She's not dying.
]有人死
No one is.
你知道你爸以前磉^@Y
Did you know your dad had been here before?
我滋烨安胖道有@地方的存在
I didn't even know this place existed until a few days ago.
你X得他在@Y质颤N
What do you think he was doing here?
考]到我是在@Y找到@的
Considering where we found this,
他是在和我做一拥氖
he was doing the same thing we are.
吾W亮的清晨之使
My bright ambassadors of morning!
此即和平之r
It is time to make peace.
卸下重
Lay down your burden.
是他 霍利尤克
Is that him... Holyoke?
服下 安o前行
Take the potion and step through quietly.
Potion?
我X得他是在他自
I think he's telling them to kill themselves.
相信湖水的力量
Believe in the power of the lake,
它⒔沂菊嫦
and it will reveal the truth.
他是耗
He was evil.
但他的信徒
But his followers?
他λ言
They did anything he told them.
言
Anything.
服下 大步前行
Take the potion and step through.
不
No.
你是l
Who are you?!
你到底想要我质颤N
What do you want from me?!
和我想要~克做的事一
The same thing I wanted from Michael...
你服奈业拿令
for you to do what I say.
你在质颤N
What are you doing?!
你在做什N
你在@Y做什N
What are you doing here?
我心你
I was worried.
你不自一人在外面
You shouldn't be out here alone.
⒘怂
Kill her.
Do it.
F在就⒘怂
Now.
Joel?
你在做什N
What are you doing?
她不死 e人就要死
Her, or someone else.
Joel.
放下你的刀
Put down the knife.
-⑺浪 -不
- Kill! - No.
⑺浪 ⑺浪
Kill her! Kill her!
他永h不放^我的
He'll never leave me alone.
l @Y]有e人
Who? There's no one here.
不要 不要
Joel, stop! Stop!
⑺浪
Kill her!
@Y]有e人
There's no one here.
一切都好起淼 深呼吸
Everything's gonna be okay. Just breathe.
]事的
It's okay.
-o你 回家注意安全 -好的
- Here you go. Get home safe. - Okay.
肯尼好
Is Kenny okay?
不 他一c都不好
No, he's not okay.
你打嗔怂的鼻子
You broke his nose,
而他也不相信你蹩_的借口
and he didn't buy your lame excuse, either.
我喝醉了
I was drunk.
你只是在Y喝了半杯啤酒
You had half a beer in the limo.
到底怎N了
What's going on, Joel?
-告V我 -我早就告V你了
- Tell me the truth. - I already told you.
我也JR~克 你F在的行楹退一模一
I knew Michael, too, and you're acting just like him.
~克把事情都藏在自己心Y @就害死了他
Michael kept everything inside, and it killed him.
如果那r他で椭的
If he'd asked for help...
害死他的是他被e人做怪物
What killed him was being seen as a freak.
他告V我父母的那一刻
The minute he told my parents,
他都他是一l了的孩子
they looked at him like a crazy kid.
拇怂再也]有用正常的眼光看他
They never looked at him the same.
我^Σ@δ愕
I will never look at you like that.
你在我面前不需要窝b
You don't have to pretend with me, Joel.
你不需要是完美o缺的
You don't have to be perfect.
告V我吧
Just talk with me.
我想要椭你
I want to help you.
我不需要你的椭
I don't need your help.
我分手吧
We're done.
嘿
Hey.
好了 弗朗茜可以正常呼吸了
Well, Francie's breathing normally again.
她]事的
She's gonna be okay.
多了你
Thanks to you.
F在所有人都去睡X吧
Now, everybody, get to bed.
大家都辛苦了
It's been a long night... for all of us.
我也是r候去赴s了Π
Guess that's my cue, too, right?
所以你要去他
So you're gonna go meet him?
要一下吧
Got to give it a shot.
我槟泸傲
I'm proud of you.
看看事情怎Nl展再F我吧
Hold the pride till we see how it goes.
嘿 布R
Uh, hey, Blair?
你f吧 ]PS
Go ahead. It's okay.
我要和你
I need to talk to you guys.
我一生都努力得
My whole life, I've tried to be strong.
就是 b作一切都很好的幼
You know, act like everything was fine,
但我]有δ坦\相待
but I haven't been honest about who I really am.
我之前有一哥哥
I used to have a brother.
~克
Michael.
~克像我@N大的r候 他自⒘
When Michael was my age, he killed himself.
他看 一些不存在的|西
He saw things that... weren't there.
~克生病了
Michael had a sickness.
而F在我也得了@病
And now I have that sickness, too.
我的z像C曾是我唯一能蛐湃蔚|西
My camera used to be the only thing that I could trust
它告V我什N是真的
to show me what's real.
它矶疾_我
It never lied.
但是F在z像C都]用了
But now the camera's not working,
而我也感X越碓皆愀
and I'm getting worse.
什N意思
What do you mean?
有男人
There's a man.
在我I地之前我就_始到他
I started seeing him before I ever came to camp.
我X得和~克看到的是同一人
I think Michael saw the same man.
他自始至K]有放^他
He never left him alone.
F在他一直跟著我 我做一些事情
And now he's following me, asking me to do things.
一些氖
Terrible things.
比如什N
Like what?
今晚他我⑺腊米
Tonight he told me to kill Amy.
否te人就死掉
Or else someone else would die.
他不是真的
He's not real.
-你知道的是 -@就是}所在
- You know that, right? - That's just it.
我再也不知道什N是真 什N是假了
I don't know what's real and what isn't anymore,
我很心
and I'm worried.
如果我找不到k法[他的
If I don't find a way to stop seeing him...
我和~克落得一拥南
I'm gonna end up just like Michael.
我得x_I地
I need to leave camp.
我需要椭
I need help.
我也湍愕
We'll help you, too, Joel.
任何事都可以
Whatever you need.
你不需要向我[m
You don't have to hide things from us.
我椭你的
We're here for you.
xx
Thanks.
我e^了什N
What'd I miss?
@一夜真L啊
It's been a night.
我也@NX得
You and me both.
我在淞盅Y碰了加勒特
I ran into Garrett in the woods.
他在查看一f小屋
He was checking out this old cabin.
我找到了一邪教首I的音
We found recordings of this cult leader
他他的追S者自
telling all of his followers to kill themselves.
霍利尤克
Holyoke.
你也知道他
You know about him, too?
加勒特我什N都不要f
Garrett told me not to say anything.
他不想我害怕
He didn't want us freaking out.
]有什N好害怕的
There's nothing to freak out about.
他已死了 但是他是很恐怖
He's dead. Still, he's pretty creepy.
怎N了
Joel, what is it?
就是他
That's him.
就是他一直跟著我
That's the man who's been following me.
如果你的哥哥]有生病呢
Joel, what if your brother wasn't sick?
如果他曾看的@人 你F在一直看的@人
What if the man he saw... the one you've been seeing...
就是霍利尤克呢
what if that was Holyoke?
是鬼魂 你_玩笑的吧
Ghosts? Seriously?
@就是我一直在f的
It's what I've been saying.
是@地方的}
It's this place.
@Y有些|西不 它t解我
There's something here. Something that knows us.
是@地方 它t解我的弱c
This place, it feeds on our weaknesses,
而霍利尤克和@肯定有什NPS
and Holyoke has something to do with it.
e_玩笑了 艾米
Come on, Amy.
就算@是真的
Even if that were true,
槭颤N只有看^他
why is Joel the only one who's seen him?
他不是唯一一^他的
He isn't the only one.
那高大的男人 是他
The Tall Man... that was him.
你也^他
You've seen him, too?
槭颤N是我
Why us?
他想要什N
What does he want?
他告V^你他想要什N
He told you what he wants.
你]有照做
You didn't listen.
他f了什N
What did he say?
他有]有告V你槭颤N他要和我f
Did he tell you why he's speaking to us?
]有
No.
他f了什N
What did he say?
他f你⑺浪的
He said you should have killed her
你e^了你的C
when you had the chance.
有人
Hello?
克瑞克特 是你
Cricket, is that you?